Guide to the Hans Reichenbach Papers, 1884-1972 ASP.1973.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Name Index, IV.
  - Frechet, Maurice (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 3)
  - Freeman, W.H. (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 15)
  - French, Leonard S. (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Frestail, A.E.Y. (Box 23, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Freund, John (Box 18, Folder 32, Item 36)
  - Freund, H. (Box 13, Folder 44, Item 2)
  - Freundlich, E.F. (Box 13, Folder 44, Item 3)
  - Freundlich, E.F. (Box 15, Folder 30, Item 2)
  - Freundlich, E.F. (Box 15, Folder 53, Item 12)
  - Freundlich, E.F. (Box 16, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Freyman (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - Fried, I.M. (Box 14, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Friederich, A. (Box 23, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Friedenwald, Jonas (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Friedmann, Hermann (Box 14, Folder 26, Item 2)
  - Frierander, Paul (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Frischeisen-Köhler, Ida (Box 16, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Frischeisen-Köhler, Max (Box 16, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Fschloudsky, V.E. (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Fues, E. (Box 14, Folder 26, Item 3)
  - Fushini, F. (Box 37, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Gaifman, Hain (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Garcia, David (Box 14, Folder 50, Item 5)
  - Garcia, David (Box 18, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Garstens, Georg (Box 25, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Gaultier, Paul (Box 13, Folder 45, Item 2)
  - Geddes, Donald Porter (Box 36, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Geiger, M. (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Geiger, M. (Box 16, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Gelb, A. (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Geldsetzer, Lutz (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Geileu, V. (Box 14, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Geissler, Willi (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - George, M.Andre (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Georgii, E. (Box 14, Folder 27, Item 2)
  - Gerhards, Karl (Box 14, Folder 50, Item 2)
  - Gerhards, Karl (Box 16, Folder 32, Item 3)
  - Gerlach, Richard (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 7)
  - Gervai, G. (Box 25, Folder 23, Item 17)
  - Gessner, Fritz (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 19)
  - Geymonat, Ludovico (Box 13, Folder 45, Item 2)
  - Gibbs, J.W. (Box 39, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Giorgi, Giovani (Box 14, Folder 27, Item 4)
  - Glatzel, D. (Box 14, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Gödel, Kurt (Box 13, Folder 13, Item 2)
  - Goebel, Prof. (Box 25, Folder 11, Item 3)
  - Goldfeld, Dr. (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Goldschmidt, Ferdinand (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Goldschmidt, Max (Box 14, Folder 27, Item 2)
  - Goldschmidt, Richard (Box 25, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Gonseth, M.F. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Goodman, Nelson (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Görland, A. (Box 15, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Görland, A. (Box 14, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Görland, A. (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 10)
  - Görland, A. (Box 16, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - Gotlieb, Bearnet (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Goyette, Ed (Box 41, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Graaf, T. (Box 41, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Grabley, Gustav (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Graf, Gottfried (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Graf, Gottfried (Box 15, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Graf, E. (Box 15, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Grailich, Elsa (Box 13, Folder 45, Item 2)
  - Grammel, R. (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Grammel (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Grelling, Kurt (Box 13, Folder 14, Item 8)
  - Grelling, Kurt (Box 13, Folder 45, Item 1)
  - Grelling, Kurt (Box 14, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Grelling, Kurt (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - Grelling, Kurt (Box 15, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Grelling, Kurt (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Grelling, Kurt (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Grelling, Kurt (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Greta, Laurell (Box 38, Folder 14, Item 2)
  - Grisel, Tante (Box 16, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Groebel, P. (Box 15, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Grommer, J. (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Gronwald, Ewald (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Gross, Herbert L. (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Gross, B. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Gross, Hans (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Grossman, R. (Box 13, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Grubelich, Greg (Box 37, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Gruf (Box 15, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Grünbaum, A.A. (Box 14, Folder 27, Item 4)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf (Box 36, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf (Box 37, Folder 24, Item 57)
  - Grünbaum, Adolf (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 3)
  - Grunsley (Box 15, Folder 54, Item 2)
  - De Gruyter, Walter & Co. (Box 14, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - De Gruyter, Walter & Co. (Box 14, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - De Gruyter, Walter & Co. (Box 14, Folder 50, Item 8)
  - De Gruyter, Walter & Co. (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 26)
  - De Gruyter, Walter & Co. (Box 15, Folder 31, Item 26)
  - De Gruyter, Walter & Co. (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - Guggenheim, Felix (Box 37, Folder 26, Item 9)
  - Guggisberg, J. (Box 23, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Gunther, Herbert (Box 26, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Gunzler, A. (Box 16, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Haas, Arthur (Box 15, Folder 55, Item 1)
  - Haber, F. (Box 14, Folder 51, Item 2)
  - Haeckel, Ernst (Box 29, Folder 17, Item 2)
  - Haering, T. (Box 15, Folder 55, Item 2)
  - Hahn, Hans (Box 14, Folder 51, Item 6)
  - Halberstaedter, H. (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 2)
  - Hamblem, David (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Harcourt, Alfred (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - Harlen, Hasse (Box 14, Folder 51, Item 2)
  - Harris, Beulah (Box 38, Folder 16, Item 3)
  - Hartmann, K.O. (Box 14, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - Hartmann, Leo (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Hartog, Phillip (Box 13, Folder 41, Item 3)
  - Hattink, J.J. (Box 41, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Hauer, Ludwig (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 2)
  - Hauptmann, Heinrich (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 2)
  - Hauser, O. (Box 14, Folder 28, Item 7)
  - Hauser, O. (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 12)
  - Hazebroek, P. (Box 37, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Hay, William (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Hearn, Gordon (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 2)
  - Heck, Lutz (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 10)
  - Heckel, Otto (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Heimuller, G. (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Heindorn, L.W. (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Heinicke, R. (Box 25, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Heinroth, Oskar (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Hellinger (Box 15, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Heisenberg, Werner (Box 13, Folder 15, Item 2)
  - Hell, Bernd (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Hempel, Carl (Box 13, Folder 15, Item 17)
  - Hempel, Carl (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 33)
  - Hempel, Carl (Box 14, Folder 28, Item 3)
  - Hempel, Carl (Box 14, Folder 51, Item 3)
  - Hempel, Carl (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Hempel, Carl (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 24)
  - Hempel, Carl (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Hempel, Carl (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Hempel, Eva (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 4)
  - Hendel, Charles (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 2)
  - Herbig, F.A. (Box 37, Folder 26, Item 35)
  - Hermann, Ernst (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Hermer, B. (Box 14, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Herzberg, A. (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - Herzberg, A. (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Herzberg, Lilly (Box 14, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Hertz, Mathild (Box 14, Folder 28, Item 2)
  - Hertz, Paul (Box 13, Folder 15, Item 3)
  - Hertz, Paul (Box 14, Folder 8, Item 5)
  - Hertz, Paul (Box 14, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Hertz, Paul (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Hertz, Paul (Box 15, Folder 32, Item 3)
  - Hertz, Paul (Box 15, Folder 55, Item 5)
  - Hertz, Paul (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 5)
  - Hertz, Paul (Box 25, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Hertz, Paul (Box 28, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Hertz, Paul (Box 28, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Hethy, Margarete (Box 16, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Heusel, Kurt (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Heussenstamm, Peter K. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Heymann, Paul (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Heyting, A. (Box 13, Folder 15, Item 3)
  - Hilbert, David (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Hilbert, David (Box 25, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Hilbert, David (Box 28, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Hilkemeier, Hugo (Box 14, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - Hilkemeier, Hugo (Box 14, Folder 28, Item 11)
  - Hirsch, Helmut (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Hirsch, Kurt (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - Hirsch, Walter (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 13)
  - Hirzel, S. (Box 15, Folder 55, Item 1)
  - Hoffer, Heinz (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Hoffer, Heinz (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Hofstadter, Albert (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 4)
  - Hohenemser, K. (Box 14, Folder 51, Item 2)
  - Hohne, Erwin (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Holtfreter, Jehannes (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - Holther, Wilbru (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 4)
  - Holton, Gerald (Box 37, Folder 21, Item 2)
  - Hook, Sidney (Box 13, Folder 16, Item 8)
  - Hook, Sidney (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 46)
  - Hook, Sidney (Box 14, Folder 51, Item 9)
  - Hook, Sidney (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 18)
  - Hooper, Sidney E. (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - Hopkins, Louis J. (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 3)
  - Horig, H. (Box 14, Folder 28, Item 5)
  - Horig, H. (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - Horkheimer, Max (Box 14, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Horkheimer, Max (Box 15, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - Horkheimer, Max (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 2)
  - Hormann, Martha (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Hornbostel, E. (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - Hornbostel, E. (Box 14, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Hosiasson, Janina (Box 13, Folder 16, Item 3)
  - Hossu, Alexander J. (Box 36, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Howe, M.B. (Box 37, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Hull, Clark L. (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Hung, Tscha (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - Hungerland, Isabel (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 5)
  - Hunt, Victor M. (Box 45, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Hurwitz, Charlotte (Box 14, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Hurwitz, H.M.B. (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 5)
  - Hurwitz, Sch. (Box 15, Folder 32, Item 3)
  - Huth, Erich (Box 14, Folder 28, Item 2)
  - Huth, Erich (Box 41, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Hutten, Ernest H. (Box 37, Folder 25, Item 22)
  - Infeld, Leopold (Box 15, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Irving, J.A. (Box 37, Folder 27, Item 5)
  - Irwin, Edman (Box 37, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Iseki, Kyosi (Box 37, Folder 27, Item 4)
  - Ives, Herbert E. (Box 37, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Jahoda, Eduard (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Janus (Box 13, Folder 47, Item 2)
  - Jaspers, K. (Box 16, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Jeffrey, E. (Box 23, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Jeffrey, E. (Box 29, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Jentzsch, Felix (Box 14, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Jensen, Paul (Box 13, Folder 17, Item 6)
  - Jensen, Paul (Box 13, Folder 47, Item 1)
  - Jeun, Tooha (Box 38, Folder 13, Item 2)
  - Joachimsohn, Kathe (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Joel, Ernst (Box 18, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Joel, Ernst (Box 44, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Johns, Walter H. (Box 37, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Johnson, Alvin (Box 37, Folder 28, Item 2)
  - Johnson, Dorothy (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Jollos, V. (Box 13, Folder 17, Item 2)
  - Jones, Howard M. (Box 18, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Jones, W.W. (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Jordan, Pascual (Box 13, Folder 17, Item 12)
  - Jordan, Pascual (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Jordan, Pascual (Box 37, Folder 28, Item 3)
  - Jørgensen, Jørgen (Box 13, Folder 17, Item 5)
  - Jørgensen, Jørgen (Box 14, Folder 52, Item 1)
  - Jørgensen, Jørgen (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Juhos, B. (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Juhos, B. (Box 37, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Jungnickel, Walter (Box 14, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Just, Florence P. (Box 37, Folder 28, Item 2)
  - Juttner, F. (Box 14, Folder 29, Item 3)
  - Juttner, F. (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - Kahnert, Walter (Box 37, Folder 26, Item 5)
  - Kaila, E. (Box 14, Folder 9, Item 4)
  - Kaila, E. (Box 14, Folder 53, Item 4)
  - Kaila, E. (Box 15, Folder 34, Item 2)
  - Kaila, E. (Box 15, Folder 56, Item 2)
  - Kaila, E. (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Kalisk, D. (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Kalisk, D. (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Kamen-Kaye, Maurice (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Kamlah, Andreas (Box 41, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Kamlah, Andreas (Box 41, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Kannwitz, Ernst (Box 29, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Kant, E. (Box 26, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Kant, E. (Box 27, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Kaplan, Abraham (Box 36, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Kaplan, Abraham (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 7)
  - Kaplan, David (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Karamete, Kemaleddin (Box 13, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - Karl, Herbert (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 8)
  - Karling, W. (Box 29, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Katz, D. (Box 13, Folder 48, Item 5)
  - Katz, D. (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (Box 14, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - Kayser-Ulstein, Ilse (Box 14, Folder 53, Item 1)
  - Kayser, Rudolf (Box 13, Folder 48, Item 13)
  - Kayser, Rudolf (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 10)
  - Kayser, Rudolf (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Ke Ting-Sui (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - Kelsen, Hans (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Kempski, Jurgen (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Kendon, F.B. (Box 13, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Kenem, Prof. (Box 15, Folder 34, Item 2)
  - Kennick, W.E. (Box 38, Folder 13, Item 2)
  - Kepler, Johannes (Box 26, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Kersey, Vierling (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Keyserling, Hermann (Box 16, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Kiepenheuer Verlag, Gustav (Box 13, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - Kindermann (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Kirchberger, Paul (Box 13, Folder 48, Item 2)
  - Kirchberger, Paul (Box 14, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - Kirk, John R. (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 7)
  - Klapper, Hugo (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Klar, Willy (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Klatt, Fritz (Box 14, Folder 53, Item 5)
  - Klaus, Thomas (Box 41, Folder 20, Item 4)
  - Klein, Frieder (Box 15, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - Klein, Frieder (Box 23, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Klima, Hans (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Kloss, Erich (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Klüpfn, Paulus (Box 44, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Kluppel (Box 44, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Knudsen, Vern O. (Box 38, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Koch, Carl V.M. (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 7)
  - Köhler, Walter (Box 14, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - Köhler, Wolfgang (Box 13, Folder 48, Item 7)
  - Köhler, Wolfgang (Box 16, Folder 35, Item 7)
  - Koehlers, K.F. (Box 15, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Kohlhammer Verlag (Box x, Folder x, Item (see Verlag W. Kohlhammer))
  - Kohlrausch, Fritz (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 4)
  - Kohn, Paul (Box 29, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Kokett, Ernst (Box 13, Folder 48, Item 2)
  - Kokett, Ernst (Box 14, Folder 53, Item 2)
  - Koller, H. (Box 14, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Koller-Aeby, H. (Box 15, Folder 34, Item 5)
  - Koloski, Janice (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Konen, Dr. (Box 14, Folder 9, Item 4)
  - Konen, Dr. (Box 14, Folder 30, Item 4)
  - Konig, E. (Box 14, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Konig, Gert (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 12)
  - Konvitz, Milton R. (Box 18, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Konvitz, Milton R. (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Kopff, A. (Box 15, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Korsch, Karl (Box 14, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Korsch, Karl (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 4)
  - Koschmieder, Erwin (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Kosteer, A. (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Kotschau, Karl (Box 14, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - Kottler, F. (Box 15, Folder 56, Item 2)
  - Kraft, Julius (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Kraft, Julius (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Kraft, Vicktor (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Krakowski, Mayer (Box 39, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Kramer, W. (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Krann, M. (Box 16, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Kranold, Hermann (Box 13, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - Kraus, Friedrich (Box 14, Folder 30, Item 2)
  - Kraus, Friedrich (Box 14, Folder 53, Item 3)
  - Krelpshmer, Ernst (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Kretschmann, Phillip M. (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Kries, J. (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 2)
  - Kroner, Prof. Dr. (Box 15, Folder 57, Item 4)
  - Kruger, Fritz (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Kruger, Lorenz (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Kruse, Cornelius (Box 18, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Kruse, Cornelius (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 6)
  - Kruseman, W.M. (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Kruseman, W.M. (Box 38, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Książka i Wiedza (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 5)
  - Kuipers, J.C. (Box 41, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - Kunze, Fritz (Box 14, Folder 30, Item 2)
  - Kunze, Fritz (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Kupelwieser, E. (Box 16, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Kurtheinz, Heirich (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Kurtz, H. (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 2)
  - Kumm, Maria (Box 14, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - Kunstwart, Prof. (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 6)
  - Kusewetter, Hollis A. (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 4)
  - Kutta, W. (Box 15, Folder 56, Item 1)
  - Kuwaki, Ayao (Box 14, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Laden, Norman (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Lafleur, Laurence (Box 39, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Lahtinen, Osvi (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Laidler, Harry W. (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Lamberty, Paul (Box 25, Folder 23, Item 8)
  - Lameere, Jean (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Lameere, Jean (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 6)
  - Lammel, Rudolf (Box 14, Folder 10, Item 4)
  - Landau, Mathias (Box 14, Folder 54, Item 2)
  - Landauer, Carl (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 2)
  - Landauer, Carl (Box 15, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Landauer, Carl (Box 16, Folder 36, Item 1)
  - Landauer, Carl (Box 44, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - Lande, Alfred (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 3)
  - Lande, Alfred (Box 15, Folder 57, Item 1)
  - Lande, Alfred (Box 15, Folder 57, Item 1)
  - Lande, Alfred (Box 16, Folder 11, Item 3)
  - Lande, Alfred (Box 37, Folder 29, Item 7)
  - Lande, Alfred (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 12)
  - Lande, Lili (Box 14, Folder 31, Item 4)
  - Lange, Luise (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Lange, O. (Box 15, Folder 57, Item 1)
  - Langer, Susanne K. (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Lanier, E.A. (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 4)
  - Lark-Horowitz, Karl (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 5)
  - Laske, Hermann (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Laue, Max von (Box 14, Folder 54, Item 3)
  - Laue, Max von (Box 15, Folder 11, Item 5)
  - Laue, Max von (Box 15, Folder 57, Item 3)
  - Laue, Max von (Box 16, Folder 11, Item 19)
  - Laue, Max von (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 9)
  - Laue, Max von (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 7)
  - Laue, Max von (Box 14, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Laurence, William L. (Box 37, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Lauwrys, J. (Box 13, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - Lazerowitz, Alice (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Lazerowitz, Morritz (Box 32, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Lecat, Maurice (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 20)
  - Lecat, Maurice (Box 15, Folder 35, Item 10)
  - Lecat, Maurice (Box 16, Folder 36, Item 2)
  - Leeuwen, J.K.W. van (Box 41, Folder 4, Item 12)
  - Lehmann, Dr. (Box 14, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Leithauser, Joachim G. (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 4)
  - Leitz, H. (Box 29, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Lenzen, Victor (Box 14, Folder 54, Item 2)
  - Lenzen, Victor (Box 15, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Lenzen, Victor (Box 37, Folder 15, Item 6)
  - Lenzen, Victor (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Leonhard, Susanne (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 3)
  - Lerner, David (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 4)
  - Leroy, Andre-Louis (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Leroi, Frank (Box 44, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Leroi, Frank (Box 44, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Lertz, W.A. (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 3)
  - Lesestunde, Dr. Hans W. Fischer (Box 14, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Levey, Irving (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Levy-Bruhl, L. (Box 15, Folder 57, Item 8)
  - Lewin, Kurt (Box 13, Folder 21, Item 3)
  - Lewin, Kurt (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 3)
  - Lewin, Kurt (Box 15, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Lewin, Kurt (Box 15, Folder 57, Item 4)
  - Lewin, Kurt (Box 16, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Lewin, Kurt (Box 16, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Lewin, Kurt (Box 16, Folder 36, Item 20)
  - Lewin, Kurt (Box 23, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Lewin, Kurt (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Lewin, Ludwig (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Lewis, Clarence Irving (Box 13, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Lewis, Clarence Irving (Box 13, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Lewis, Clarence Irving (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 7)
  - Lewis, Clarence Irving (Box 14, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Lewis, Clarence Irving (Box 14, Folder 54, Item 3)
  - Lewis, Clarence Irving (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 15)
  - Lichtenstein, L. (Box 14, Folder 54, Item 6)
  - Lichtenstein, Z. (Box 13, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Liebert, Arthur (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 7)
  - Liebert, Arthur (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 5)
  - Lilienthal, Philip (Box 36, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Lindenbaum-Hosiasson, Janina (Box 13, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - Lindenbaum-Hosiasson, Janina (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Lindt, Rich (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Lipman, Otto (Box 15, Folder 57, Item 8)
  - Lipsius, F. (Box 14, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Loeb and Loeb (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - Loedel, E. (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Lotz, John (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Lewy, Heinrich (Box 13, Folder 22, Item 8)
  - Loewenfeld, W. (Box 14, Folder 10, Item 4)
  - Loewenfeld, W. (Box 15, Folder 35, Item 3)
  - Loewenberg, J. (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 3)
  - Lorentz, Hans (Box 14, Folder 10, Item 2)
  - Lorentz, Hans (Box 15, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - London, Fritz (Box 14, Folder 10, Item 2)
  - London, Fritz (Box 37, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - London, Fritz (Box 39, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - London, Fritz (Box 15, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Loose, Hans-Walter (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Lorimer, Walter L.M. (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Looy, Herman Direktor van (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Louis, Paul (Box 38, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Lowith, Karl (Box 13, Folder 49, Item 5)
  - Lubbert, G. (Box 29, Folder 7, Item 8)
  - Ludorff, Eduard (Box 25, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Luserke, M. (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - Lutero, Toribio Martin (Box 18, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Lyman, Lloyd (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Lyman, Lloyd (Box 36, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Mach, Ernst (Box 29, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Mahnke, Dietrich (Box 16, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Mahnke, Dietrich (Box 16, Folder 37, Item 3)
  - Maier, Heinrich (Box 14, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Malche, A. (Box 13, Folder 50, Item 7)
  - Malisoff, W.M. (Box 13, Folder 23, Item 3)
  - Malisoff, W.M. (Box 13, Folder 50, Item 4)
  - Malisoff, W.M. (Box 13, Folder 53, Item 2)
  - Malloch, J.M. (Box 36, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Mally (Box 24, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Mandel, Heinrich (Box 14, Folder 55, Item 2)
  - Mandelbaum, Maurice (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 5)
  - Manheim, Karl (Box 13, Folder 50, Item 4)
  - Mannsdorf, Otto (Box 29, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Marbe, K. (Box 13, Folder 50, Item 1)
  - Marck, Siegfried (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Marcus, Ruth Barcan (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 2)
  - Marcuse, Dr. A. (Box 14, Folder 32, Item 6)
  - Margenau, Henry (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 2)
  - Marhenke, Paul (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 2)
  - Marhenke, Paul (Box 38, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Marinel, I. (Box 38, Folder 17, Item 3)
  - Maron, Bill (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Maron, Melvin (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Marschak, Jacob (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 2)
  - Martin, R.M. (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Marx, Ernst (Box 13, Folder 50, Item 2)
  - Marzynski, G. (Box 14, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Marzynski, G. (Box 14, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Masters, Warner (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - Mathias, James (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - Mathias, Oskar (Box 14, Folder 55, Item 6)
  - May, Eduard (Box 13, Folder 50, Item 3)
  - Mayer-Kaupp, H. (Box 17, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - McCracken, Charles (Box 37, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - McCracken, Henry Noble (Box 37, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - McDougall, William (Box 17, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - McGuigan, F.J. (Box 36, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - McKinsey, J.C.C. (Box 37, Folder 32, Item 4)
  - McLarney, E.I. (Box 18, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Mechel, Johana (Box 29, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Mehlberg, Henry (Box 13, Folder 50, Item 1)
  - Mehmke, A. (Box 13, Folder 50, Item 2)
  - Mehmer, Herman (Box 15, Folder 36, Item 6)
  - Mehr, Erich (Box 14, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 13, Folder 24, Item 61)
  - Meiner, Felix, (4) (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 14, Folder 11, Item 9)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 14, Folder 32, Item 4)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 15, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 25, Folder 2, Item 24)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 16)
  - Melden, A.I. (Box 37, Folder 34, Item 2)
  - Melden, A.I. (Box 38, Folder 12, Item 1)